Guide to the Toba Pato Tucker Photographs and Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Re Viewing the American Landscape West & Southwest, 2012-2015; Series V; (29 boxes)
  - Portfolio #1
    - Inkjet prints, 17 inches by 22 inches
      - Colorado
        - Garden of the Gods - Colorado Springs
          - Untitled (No. 1992), 2012 (Box 256 (Oversize), Folder 3472)
          - Seal and Bear Rocks (No. 2032), 2012 (Box 256 (Oversize), Folder 3473)
          - Cathedral Spires Rocks, on left (No. 2034), 2012 (Box 256 (Oversize), Folder 3474)
          - Gateway Rocks, looking West to Pikes Peak (No. 2065), 2012 (Box 256 (Oversize), Folder 3475)
          - Gateway Rocks, looking West to Pikes Peak (No. 2123), 2012 (Box 256 (Oversize), Folder 3476)
        - Colorado National Monument - Fruita
          - Canyon Rim Trail, Rim Rock Drive (No. 2198), 2012 (Box 257 (Oversize), Folder 3477)
          - The Uncompahgre Plateau - Wingate Sandstone, Rim Rock Drive (No. 2201), 2012 (Box 257 (Oversize), Folder 3478)
          - Atop the Uncompahgre Plateau - Rim Rock Drive (No. 2203), 2012 (Box 257 (Oversize), Folder 3479)
          - Independent Monument View - Rim Rock Drive (No. 2206), 2012 (Box 257 (Oversize), Folder 3480)
          - Grand View - Grand Junction and Colorado River, from Rim Rock Drive (No. 2209), 2012 (Box 257 (Oversize), Folder 3481)
          - From Rim Rock Drive (No. 2216), 2012 (Box 257 (Oversize), Folder 3482)
          - Cold Shivers Point, Colorado River, left - Rim Rock Drive (No. 2217), 2012 (Box 257 (Oversize), Folder 3483)
          - Rim Rock Drive (No. 2218), 2012 (Box 257 (Oversize), Folder 3484)
          - Above the Grand Valley of the Colorado River, top of Rim Rock Drive (No. 2226), 2012 (Box 257 (Oversize), Folder 3485)
      - Anasazi Ruins
        Organized by the photographer with a group of prints of sites in Mesa Verde, Monument Valley, and Chaco Canyon followed by prints under nine headings:
        - Mesa Verde, Colorado - Balcony House (No. 0003), 2010 (Box 257 (Oversize), Folder 3486)
        - Mesa Verde, Colorado - Cliff Palace (No. 0108), 2010 (Box 257 (Oversize), Folder 3487)
        - Monument Valley, Utah - Hogan, reconstructed (Top, No. 0013, Bottom, No. 0015), 2010 (Box 257 (Oversize), Folder 3488)
          Two images on one sheet. Unsigned and dated.
        - Chaco Canyon, New Mexico - Pueblo Bonito, interior (No. 0064), 2010 (Box 257 (Oversize), Folder 3489)
        - Chaco Canyon, New Mexico - Pueblo Bonito, interior (No. 0073), 2010 (Box 257 (Oversize), Folder 3490)
        - Pueblo of Salmon, Bloomfield, New Mexico
          Photographs of the Salmon Site
          - Untitled (No. 2536), 2012 (Box 258 (Oversize), Folder 3491)
          - Untitled (No. 2548), 2012 (Box 258 (Oversize), Folder 3492)
          - Kiva (No. 2570), 2012 (Box 258 (Oversize), Folder 3493)
          - Untitled (No. 2577), 2012 (Box 258 (Oversize), Folder 3494)
        - Pueblo of Aztec, Aztec, New Mexico
          Photographs of Aztec Ruins National Monument
          - Untitled (No. 2593), 2012 (Box 258 (Oversize), Folder 3495)
          - Untitled (No. 2595), 2012 (Box 258 (Oversize), Folder 3496)
          - Kiva (No. 2598), 2012 (Box 258 (Oversize), Folder 3497)
          - The Great Kiva, Reconstructed (No. 2600), 2012 (Box 258 (Oversize), Folder 3498)
          - Untitled (No. 2604), 2012 (Box 258 (Oversize), Folder 3499)
          - Untitled (No. 2636), 2012 (Box 258 (Oversize), Folder 3500)
        - Pueblo of Escalante on site of Anasazi Heritage Center, north of Cortez, Colorado
          - Montezuma Valley & La Plata Mountains (No. 2702), 2012 (Box 258 (Oversize), Folder 3501)
          - Untitled (No. 2703), 2012 (Box 258 (Oversize), Folder 3502)
          - Untitled (No. 2705), 2012 (Box 258 (Oversize), Folder 3503)
        - Pueblo of Escalante on site of Anasazi Heritage Center (rear), north of Cortez, Colorado
          - Kiva (No. 2710), 2012 (Box 258 (Oversize), Folder 3504)
        - Pueblo of Lowry with Protective Roof - Road CC Route 491 - Pleasant View Colorado
          Photographs of Lowry Pueblo Ruins.
          - Untitled (No. 2716), 2012 (Box 258 (Oversize), Folder 3505)
          - "T" shaped doorway, left (No. 2723), 2012 (Box 258 (Oversize), Folder 3506)
        - Pueblo of Painted Hand, near Pleasant View, Colorado, Route 491 Road 10
          - The Great Sage Plain (No. 2739), 2012 (Box 258 (Oversize), Folder 3507)
        - Hovenweep, Utah-Colorado Border west of Cortez, Colorado
          Photographs of Hovenweep National Monument.
          - Twin Towers & Rim Rock House, right (No. 2806), 2012 (Box 259 (Oversize), Folder 3508)
          - Stronghold House, center - Twin Towers, left - Hovenweep House, distance (No. 2812), 2012 (Box 259 (Oversize), Folder 3509)
          - Hovenweep Castle - Hovenweep House, background (photographer's shadow lower right) (No. 2828), 2012 (Box 259 (Oversize), Folder 3510)
          - Hovenweep Castle (No. 2833), 2012 (Box 259 (Oversize), Folder 3511)
          - Hovenweep House (No. 2841), 2012 (Box 259 (Oversize), Folder 3512)
          - Square Tower (No. 2841), 2012 (Box 259 (Oversize), Folder 3513)
          - Tower Point (No. 2841), 2012 (Box 259 (Oversize), Folder 3514)
          - Trail to Hovenweep Castle - Hovenweep House, right (No. 2871), 2012 (Box 259 (Oversize), Folder 3515)
      - Little Colorado River
        - Gorge of the Little Colorado River - Between The Grand Canyon and Cameron, Arizona on Route 64 (No. 3488), 2012 (Box 259 (Oversize), Folder 3516)
        - The Little Colorado River - Cameron, Arizona on Route 89 - Dry Riverbed (No. 3492), 2012 (Box 259 (Oversize), Folder 3517)
        - The Little Colorado River - Cameron, Arizona on Route 89 - Dry Riverbed (No. 3494), 2012 (Box 259 (Oversize), Folder 3518)
        - The Little Colorado River - Cameron, Arizona on Route 89 - Dry Riverbed (No. 3497), 2012 (Box 259 (Oversize), Folder 3519)
      - Hopi Landscape, Arizona
        - Route 160 North East to Tuba City - Moenkopi Plateau (No. 3501), 2012 (Box 259 (Oversize), Folder 3520)
        - The Moenkopi Plateau, looking South from Highway 264 (No. 3508), 2012 (Box 259 (Oversize), Folder 3521)
      - Hubbell Trading Post, Arizona
        - Hubbell Trading Post, Since 1878 - Between Steamboat and Ganado, Arizona (No. 3531), 2012 (Box 259 (Oversize), Folder 3522)
        - Interleaving sheets
          Sheets of paper, 11 inches by 22 inches, that separated descrete groups of prints upon accession.
    - Inkjet prints, 8.5 inches by 11 inches
      Organized by the photographer under three headings: Colorado, Anasazi Ruins, and En Route and In Arizona, then by sites she visited sequentially at these broader locations.
      - Colorado
        - Silverton
          - Sultan Mountain, Turk's Head Point on left (No. 0910), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3523)
          - City Hall [built] circa 1908, looking North on Green Street (formerly Main Street), Boulder Mountain "Storm Peak" (No. 0920), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3524)
          - Looking South on Blair Street - Sultan Mountain, Turk's Head on left (No. 0943), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3525)
          - Looking Southwest on Reese Street - Library [built] circa 1906 on left with steeple, Andrew Carnegie Building (No. 0957), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3526)
          - Looking North on Reese Street - Boulder Mountain "Storm Peak" (No. 0958), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3527)
          - Looking Southwest on 12th Street and Blair Street (No. 0964), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3528)
          - Looking West from outside of town on 12th Street (No. 0997), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3529)
          - Mine with tailings, Animas River (No. 1021), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3530)
        - Ouray
          Title for each print also includes statement: City originally named "Uncompahgre," the Ute Indian word for "hot water springs."
          - Main Street - San Juan Mountains of the Rocky Mountain Range (No. 1057), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3531)
          - "The Gap," San Juan Mountains of the Rocky Mountain Range (No. 1117), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3532)
          - Route 550 - San Juan Mountains of the Rocky Mountain Range (No. 1119), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3533)
        - Telluride
          - Colorado Street - San Juan Mountains, Rocky Mountain Range (No. 1162), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3534)
        - Gunnison River
          - Middle Bridge (No. 1223), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3535)
          - Narrow Point Dam (No. 1270), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3536)
        - Leadville
          - Leadville Colorado & Southern Railroad station, County Road 10 (No. 1313), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3537)
          - Entrance to Matchless Mine, Trailings Piles, left (No. 1322), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3538)
          - Matchless Mine, Non-working (No. 1327), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3539)
          - Robert E. [Lee] Mine, Non-working (No. 1335), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3540)
          - Robert E. Lee Mine, Non-working (No. 1341), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3541)
          - Drilling Rocks used in yearly competition, Mine Headframe over Shaft, Slag, from Smelters Row (black pile on left) (No. 1361), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3542)
        - Pikes Peak
          - Rim Drive (No. 1688), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3543)
          - Rim Drive (No. 1754), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3544)
          - Rim Drive (No. 1756), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3545)
          - Rim Drive (No. 1772), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3546)
          - Cog Railway Tracks (No. 1785), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3547)
          - Summit "Constructed 1873" (No. 1793), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3548)
          - Summit Marker, 14,100 Feet (No. 1801), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3549)
        - Manitou Springs - Cave of the Winds
          - Entrance (No. 1837), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3550)
          - Observation Deck above Williams Canyon (No. 18363), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3551)
          - Original Entrance, Ranger Guide (No. 1880), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3552)
        - Waldo Canyon - Colorado Springs
          - Fire Closes National Forest (No. 1894), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3553)
        - Garden of the Gods - Colorado Springs
          - Segway Two Wheel Standup Scooters (No. 1932), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3554)
          - Seal & Bear (No. 2026), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3555)
          - Untitled (No. 2133), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3556)
      - Anasazi Ruins
        Organized by the photographer under nine headings:
        - Pueblo of Salmon, Bloomfield, New Mexico
          - Salmon Family Pioneer Homestead (No. 2527), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3557)
          - Kiva (No. 2563), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3558)
          - Untitled (No. 2579), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3559)
          - Untitled (No. 2582), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3560)
        - Pueblo of Aztec, Aztec, New Mexico
          - Untitled (No. 2626), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3561)
          - Reconstructed Kiva, left (No. 2662), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3562)
          - Kiva (No. 2668), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3563)
          - The Great Kiva, Re-constructed, interior (No. 2696), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3564)
        - Pueblo of Lowry with Protective Roof - Road CC Route 491 - Pleasant View Colorado
          - Untitled (No. 2719), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3565)
        - Enroute to Painted Hands Ruins outside Cortez, Colorado
          - Untitled (No. 2726), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3566)
          - Hon tsomo "Sleeping Ute mountain" (No. 2727), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3567)
          - Untitled (No. 2731), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3568)
        - Painted Hand Pueblo, near Pleasant view, Colorado - Route 491 Road 10
          - Great Sage Plain, Hon stomo "Sleeping Ute Mountain" (No. 2738), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3569)
      - En Route To and In Arizona
        - En Route from Hovenweep to Arizona
          - Sleeping Ute Mountain - Utah-Colorado border west of Cortez, Colorado (No. 2872), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3570)
          - Sleeping Ute Mountain - Utah-Colorado border west of Cortez, Colorado (No. 2880), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3571)
        - Cameron, Arizona - Route 160 to Tuba City
          - Untitled (No. 3504), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3572)
          - Untitled (No. 3505), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3573)
        - Hubbell Trading Post, Since 1878 - Between Steamboat and Ganado, Arizona
          - Untitled (No. 3520), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3574)
          - Untitled (No. 3527), 2012 (Box 260, Folder 3575)
    - Reference Inkjet Prints, 8.5 inches by 11 inches
      Organized under two headings: Portraits of Photographers and Photographs in Colorado by William Henry Jackson.
      - Portraits of Photographers
        - Toba Pato Tucker, Photographing - Death Valley, California, 2010 (Box 261, Folder 3576)
          Photograph by Claudio Santini.
        - William Henry Jackson, printed 2012; image created 1872 (Box 261, Folder 3577)
          Heavily retouched portrait of Jackson with source cited as the United States National Park Service on the print.
        - William Henry Jackson Photographing in the Field, printed 2012; image created 1872 (Box 261, Folder 3578)
          View of Jackson and his assistant Charles R. Campbell with their dark tent on the west side of the Teton Range in Wyoming.
      - Photographs in Colorado by William Henry Jackson
        Inkjet prints from digital surrogates of original prints held by the Beinecke Rare Book & Manuscript Library, except where noted, that served as references for photographs by Tucker. Image numbers to digital surrogates referenced on rectos of prints no longer referenced in the Digital Collections. Titles from inscriptions in negatives except where noted. Occasionally, image titles in this guide reflect titles applied by the original photographer rather than later by Tucker.
        Arranged by the Tucker under eleven headings: Silverton, Ouray, Telluride, Gunnison River, Leadville, Pikes Peak - Colorado Springs, Manitou Springs, Manitou Springs - Cave of the Winds, Garden of the Gods - Colorado Springs, Monument Park - El Paso County, and Hovenweep, Utah-Colorado Border west of Cortez, Colorado.
        - Silverton
          - Cañon of the Rio Las Animas (No. 3260), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3579)
            Original print in William Henry Jackson, Photographs of Colorado, Call number WA Photos 10. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 0881-1030.
          - Silverton (No. 3265), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3580)
          - Silverton (No. 3256), printed 2012; image created circa 1870-1879 (Box 261, Folder 3581)
            Original print in William Henry Jackson, Rocky Mountain Views (Denver, Colorado, 1870-1879), Call number Zc10 870ja. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 0881-1030.
          - Main St. Silverton (No. 2890), printed 2012; image created circa 1890-1900 (Box 261, Folder 3582)
            From a digital surrogate in the Digital Collections of Denver Public Library. Original print in W. H. Jackson Sample Album. Colorado Book IV. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 0932.
          - Howardville, Baker's Park (No. 184), printed 2012; image created circa 1874-1880 (Box 261, Folder 3583)
            View of Howardsville, a settlement at Bakers Park along the Animas River. From a digital surrogate in the Digital Collections of Denver Public Library. Original print in W. H. Jackson Sample Album. Colorado Book VII. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 0895.
        - Ouray
          - Marshall Pass and Mt. Ouray (No. 1009), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3584)
            Original print in William Henry Jackson, Photographs of Colorado, Call number WA Photos 10. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 1057-1129.
          - Summit of Marshall Pass (No. 1006), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3585)
          - Ouray, (Oo-ray), The Rocky Mountains (No. 26), printed 2012; image created circa 1874 (Box 261, Folder 3586)
            Original print in Photographs of Colorado, compiled by Ernest Ingersoll (1889), Call number ZZc49 889ph. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 1057-1129.
          - Ouray, from the West, The Rocky Mountains (No. 27), printed 2012; image created circa 1874 (Box 261, Folder 3587)
          - Uncompahgre Canon, near Ouray, The Rocky Mountains (No. 29), printed 2012; image created circa 1874 (Box 261, Folder 3588)
          - Climbing Aspen Mountain, At Ouray, Near Salida, Looking Northwest, The Rocky Mountains (No. 36), printed 2012; images created circa 1874 (Box 261, Folder 3589)
            Four discrete original prints. Original prints in Photographs of Colorado, compiled by Ernest Ingersoll (1889), Call number ZZc49 889ph. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 1057-1129.
          - Toll Gate at Bear Creek Falls (No. 1399), printed 2012; image created circa 1880-1890 (Box 261, Folder 3590)
            From a digital surrogate in the Digital Collections of Denver Public Library. Original print in W. H. Jackson Sample Album. Colorado Book VIII. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 1129.
          - Toll Gate, Bear Creek Falls (No. 1188), printed 2012; image created circa 1882-1900 (Box 261, Folder 3591)
            From a digital surrogate in the Digital Collections of Denver Public Library. From original negative in History Colorado, William Henry Jackson Collection. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 1129.
        - Telluride
          - Main Street, Telluride, Colorado, printed 2012; image created circa 1900-1910 (Box 261, Folder 3592)
            Photograph by Joseph B. Byers. From a digital surrogate in the Digital Collections of Denver Public Library. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 1155-1162.
        - Gunnison River
          - Currecanti Needle, Black Canyon of the Gunnison (No. 1081), printed 2012; image created circa 1878-1898 (Box 261, Folder 3593)
            Original print in Mammoth Plate Photographs of the North American West, Call number WA Photos Folio 1. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 1191-1282.
        - Leadville
          - Buena Vista. Coaches for Leadville, printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3594)
            Original print in William Henry Jackson, Photographs of Colorado, Call number WA Photos 10. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 1293-1361.
          - Leadville, Colorado (No. 1201), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3595)
          - View from the Court House, Leadville (No. 1211), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3596)
          - Leadville, from Carbonate Hill (No. 1203), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3597)
          - Harrison Avenue, Leadville (No. 1213), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3598)
          - The Robert E. Lee Mine, Leadville (No. 1225), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3599)
          - Untitled (No Number), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3600)
            View of a hydraulic mining operation in Leadville, Colorado. Title in negative scratched out. Image also known as Grant Smelter (No. 1217). Original print in William Henry Jackson, Photographs of Colorado, Call number WA Photos 10. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 1293-1361.
        - Pikes Peak - Colorado Springs
          - We Helped to Build Pike's Peak Railroad (No. 1074), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3601)
            Original print in William Henry Jackson, Photographs of Colorado, Call number WA Photos 10. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 1664-1801.
          - U.S. Signal Station on Pike's Peak (No. 421), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3602)
          - Sun Rise, Pike's Peak (No. 434), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3603)
          - Sunrise, Pike's Peak (No. 1068), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3604)
          - The Bottomless Pit, Pike's Peak (No. 690), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3605)
          - U.S. Signal Station on Pike's Peak (No. 421), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3606)
          - Pike's Peak Trail, "Timber Line" (No. 425), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3607)
        - Manitou Springs
          - Manitou (No. 1050), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3608)
            Original print in William Henry Jackson, Photographs of Colorado, Call number WA Photos 10. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 1805 and 1876.
        - Manitou Springs - Cave of the Winds
          - Approach to Cave of the Winds, William's Canon (No. 1004), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3609)
            Original print in William Henry Jackson, Photographs of Colorado, Call number WA Photos 10. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 1837-1880.
          - Entrance to Cave of the Winds (No. 414), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3610)
          - Pike's Peak Trail, The Rocky Mountains (No. 14), printed 2012; images created circa 1874 (Box 261, Folder 3611)
            Two discrete original prints. Original prints in Photographs of Colorado, compiled by Ernest Ingersoll (1889), Call number ZZc49 889ph. Images provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 1664-1801.
        - Garden of the Gods - Colorado Springs
          - Siamese Twins (No. 603), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3612)
            Original print in William Henry Jackson, Photographs of Colorado, Call number WA Photos 10. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 1908-2123.
          - Garden of the Gods (No. 768), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3613)
          - Cathedral Spires, Garden of the Gods (No. 1403), printed 2012; image created circa 1870 (Box 261, Folder 3614)
            Original print in William Henry Jackson, Photographs of Colorado, Call number WA Photos 202. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 1908-2123.
          - Balanced Rock, Garden of the Gods (No. 1419), printed 2012; image created circa 1870 (Box 261, Folder 3615)
          - Gateway to the Garden of the Gods and Pike's Peak (No. 1411), printed 2012; image created circa 1870 (Box 261, Folder 3616)
          - The Native, Seal and Bear, Garden of the Gods (No. 1409), printed 2012; image created circa 1870 (Box 261, Folder 3617)
          - Garden of the Gods (No. 1408), printed 2012; image created circa 1885 (Box 261, Folder 3618)
            Original print in Mammoth Plate Photographs of the North American West, Call number WA Photos Folio 1. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 1908-2123.
          - Cathedral Spires, Garden of the Gods (No. 1163), printed 2012; image created circa 1885 (Box 261, Folder 3619)
          - Gateway, Garden of the Gods (No. 1031), printed 2012; image created circa 1885 (Box 261, Folder 3620)
          - Gateway, Pike's Peak from the Garden of the Gods (No. 1078), printed 2012; image created circa 1885 (Box 261, Folder 3621)
          - Seal and Bear Rocks, Garden of the Gods (No. 1194), printed 2012; image created circa 1885 (Box 261, Folder 3622)
          - Tower of Babel (No. 1007), printed 2012; image created circa 1885 (Box 261, Folder 3622A)
          - The Bear and Seal: Garden of the Gods and Pulpit Rock: Ute Pass, The Rocky Mountains (No. 9), printed 2012; images created circa 1874 (Box 261, Folder 3623)
            Two discrete original prints. Original prints in Photographs of Colorado, compiled by Ernest Ingersoll (1889), Call number ZZc49 889ph. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 1908-2123.